#### Rafael Zoldan

(054) 2256204 zoldan.rafael@gmail.com

### **Profiles:**





Rafazoldan.com

## Languages:

Spanish (mother tongue) English (fluent) Hebrew (fluent)

#### **Education:**

2019

Netcraft Academy: Full Stack Development course

2011 - 2014

The COLLMAN: Master in **Business Administration** 

2001 - 2006

Universidad San Francisco de Quito:BA - Advertising & Communications Minor in photography

## Summary

I'm a passionate, motivated and resourceful Full-Stack developer. Responsible and hard working team player with great independent capabilities; quick learner, curious and thrilled by new challenges.

I've been developing for **3 years**, though with formal education only for one.

#### Skills

HTML 5, CSS 3, Saas Javascript, ES6 Node.js, MongoDB, Python React Webpack Git

# **Experience:**

12/2019 - Present

Full Stack Developer | Sentinel 7

Building a startup project with social impact In charge of front end development using: React, ES6, Firebase, git, agile methodology

04/2018 - 10/2019

**VP Digital Operations and Marketing** Recovery Health (Strokemark.com)

Setup, and management of all digital systems and processes including Wordpress, Hubspot, Twilio, Gsuite, Tagmanager, Datastudio, Zendesk, Adwords, Facebook, Twitter, Mailchimp.

Team management leading our client service representatives and third party software developers.



10/2010 - 12/2017

**Operations Director and Technical Support Albert Technologies LTD** 

In charge of customer Technical Support and API integration.

In charge of Innovation Projects including research, design, proof of concept, budget management, lead development with the R&D team.

Manage third party systems (Adwords, Facebook, CRM, Dashboard, ad servers, video players, tracking systems, reporting tools) serving as technical support.

Trained all new employees on RTB, tracking, and platforms usage